[Music]
we're off to our second Meetup just meet
up in Kansas City Missouri City was
learning over in Kansas right now this
state right now what thank you
yeah get there of course of course of
course
this this leg of the trip is being
sponsored all that we're going to do the
shoutouts to Smith
yeah
I don't think he's done yet yeah we're
an hour ahead 941 woke up so early
woke up so early all
somewhere else
driving well here
yeah where we going to Kansas City
another makers baby
[Music]
or something
ever argue about a hammer slag
chairman
it's on
guys Traer is really pouring oh yo you
know what is I think on this trip but
Jen I did this last time we can see the
world's largest prairie dog movie Lee no
you know the band question right yeah
the band question is don't ask us what
car this works on or don't ask
yeah if you want to know what car works
oh that's fine that's something get up
but don't ask when it will at work on my
Ford Mustang GT 2004 I don't know
any news scope visa it would be it would
be nice and some people this is a
legitimate question does open pilot
voyage or factory warranty no so the way
warranties work so there's a long
history of a modifying automotive
outside of the dealership right in order
for them to void your warranty they have
to show that the component that they
would be replacing under your warranty
was actually broken by the aftermarket
module installed so for example if
you're you know head gasket place now if
you you know change the boost pressure
on your engine your head gasket flows
they're gonna look at you but allow me
most mods are like engine my most mods
are like edgy budget yeah so if you do
like an engine model like you know their
air conditioning breaks you know they
gotta fix your air conditioning right
well you probably want to turn off your
mom
oh yeah you know it says it's just like
jailbreaking your phone just
jailbreaking your iPhone 4G warranty now
just restored
we're driving a rap for there's actually
even way more consumer protection laws
yeah we've 75 scobie's that's way more
than what just like creepy a comrade
yeah be nice if like I can just say like
yo cargo around the truck okee on plot a
course around that truck is it clear on
the left so we don't sell any
self-driving kits if we sell we sell
hardware and we give away software so
this is a demo so we have we have ways
up here we got we got six hours 37
minutes to Kansas City doesn't have
reception right now you can live
t-mobile down Spotify over here people
sounded out just in case no one's asking
where we'll be in Pittsburgh we've been
doing any snow
how much is the hardware for the Ravel
so this - game development kid the Aeon
is for sale for $6.99 $6.99 you at shop
around the wall
well so you have a panda in this car to
interface with the car that's $99 trucks
and we gonna make our cover look fancy
like everyone else I like liars
even as pet Ricardo hates its power wire
gonna make our wire how our thoughts
looking for the harder ones none of them
it's all software best
hence you just need your panda to
interface
with the radar in the car you need a
giraffe carrier board for your panda so
this car has TS SP it means it has
adaptive cruise control and Lane Assist
system so using those things you can
actually control the console
it's Frodo strapped to a child seat no
we got Frodo now yes these these are
really comfy in the front seat as dude
last night our friend rented a out EA
for from silver car and that might be
the flagship Baxter nicer than oh my god
I don't think of the Model S it's like a
luxury car I think it's nice a fantastic
I don't see the speakers are better than
this shitty other speakers are better
than that
yeah it was like nothing to do they just
like look around yeah like we're cutting
right through chaos right but I hope you
like Prairie
people like Missouri stole Kansas City
like isn't that a bigger we stole half
of it they actually did Alisa yeah no
Jimmy everybody great degrade Missouri
Kansas war of 1842 and stole half the
city yeah
now mazury mazury mazury won hands down
man Missouri's like but we're nice I
mean it it's called Kansas City so will
you keep the shitty ass this is real
I'm not even I'm not even lying
about this go to hungry you go to
Budapest and
you've been the
they have stuck pepper
Oh heroes heroes and crepes cheapest
Kotick while driving
Nicole driving yeah yeah that was fun
racetrack on closed courses you can call
your traffic yeah still scary though you
two that don't open her up yeah like
owning and driving
we're just listening to physics lectures
hell yeah black bull's eye calls which I
can't see him
that's right
just built a lot of tiny parts in there
in space and assemble them
where's our Dyson Sphere
any good questions they have you got
everything you got to read the comments
wait is that somebody asking about their
see every single question but here's the
thing guys were not answering questions
about supported cars just because you
can find that on the your car's gonna be
supported you guys are like the
jailbreak people who would always add
when isn't gonna work on my iphone 3gs
not a good am I gonna make it work on
your car
rustling a little bit over to the left
there yeah lady 175 deal with they're
gonna pull me over going 6 miles over
the limit 7900 their iPhone they want to
run over on their iPhone I'm distracted
site is that's kind of cool way right
away what I taught you
yeah we're out of the morning he
implemented its controls yeah
what
we live in a better place if everyone
read Atlas Shrugged and one of the kids
who didn't grew up out of drugs the
world needs a solution what a doubt it's
hogs and peas and stuff that you thought
Molly Dobbs with 25 new parties to the
flip cup and beer pong your resume
skills the food clearing the we've hit
in the night light out with girls well
Gawker and Facebook are destroying the
world Facebook yeah if you wouldn't let
your principal crack yeah I agree that
wasn't a freestyle that was totally how
do you define free stuff I obviously
wrote that before people go on sway in
the morning and they freestyle they
totally wrote that except for a
riff raff he actually just made his
up
but then but like that it was been
arrows a word that they throw out some
explaining there isn't work but you
still have scope ease
because a little delay does not start
out working tell him it was okay it
was they're gonna like my freestyle
Scooby told me the weirdest coppice
let's go come on George what you got go
see me walk around has to be kind of
mopey then I perk up at the sight of all
my scope beyond
drive it to a dark town all of the signs
neon but none of them is brightest my
shiny new comedy night stop
sit here
Oh Your Honor Ilan coffee got him
feeling himself these are the comments I
don't read out but not know it's
actually a fun game you go your suit
Cilic random word generator you just had
to make up for style because all the
random words free sound on the front of
people's heart
do this yeah just my room and like you
guys guess what sweet and you just
didn't but like you know like one in
three is like damn this fire and they're
like the other ones are like say some
gibberish yo but sure own does this your
own does
yeah grab our guy demo rap battles oh
gotta laugh what a good ass
keep it in your room young man I'm gonna
get a 16 I'm just gonna say I'm not even
gonna say his name right now but I'm
about to be I'm about to feature on some
big-name rapper now I'm not going
to kiss doesn't happen no see my rap
career 2018 is gonna be yeah two zeroes
ma'am yeah it's like James Dean with two
E's
threes yeah I was originally gonna be
Tom Cruise to us but my buddy
his name is goose and he's like I think
of people often come haven't heard of
any other big smalls gone Papa is the
same guy who beats Big Creek way god
what's pretty crass or a big frat secret
open pilot errors on rav4 hybrid
fix it pull request descent photographs
snip
yeah Big KRIT big Chris pretty good
is still relevant pigs yeah he's big
guys from Mike place from Mississippi
I'm sorry
there what else happens in Missouri
please I've ever really been a miss
orders can't because you want to know
we are still account I'm telling you the
only thing in Kansas is the world's
largest prairie dog it's about half way
to give the city stop there at leggins
5:00 6:00 p.m. right as the Sun was
going down both Kansas City around 10:00
went to the Apple store the next morning
tax-free oh we gotta stop the episodes
tax-free in Kansas no I was looking a
special holiday in Kansas where's
Dorothy's house yeah we got to give this
some air pods
their slogan live free or die there's no
place you live Adi showed Omaha tomorrow
morning hell yeah thing is we're - we're
waiting to hear back from a Kansas TV
station so if we do that we can make it
folks if we do that if you don't do that
we'd love to do a radio show in the
morning in Omaha absolutely we call it
because we have our beat up at 2:00 p.m.
but our meet ups at 2:00 p.m. we're
going to meet up at 10:00 a.m. the next
day so and that's three hours - so we
can do our thing
dealership and then the school but oh
yeah guys we're going to Toyota
dealership today yeah and they're like
contacting media for us oh sure I'll
totally let you know I let me let me see
if I have service to check that you know
this wait when are we going to us
are we gonna let the press turn
I think it's a pair like this it could
be
pretty well that's a lot better than
stopped
don't don't expect a self-driving car
you can sleep
absolutely so far in the periscope we've
got two disengages
and should be
delicious are we gonna let
fourth grade we don't have a fourth
grader drive now that's illegal even in
South Dakota I tell now what is the
driving age knowing like a lass gets
like 12 or something
man what are you doing Alaska right
through you paid to live unless you pay
to live in
people
so they can afford to pay him oh yeah
nice job not going for the exit yes
no we don't meet with legislators we
don't meet with politics we don't we
don't we are we are we are friends with
politicians but the kind of friends at
arm's length you can buy our product
from Russia we can ship it to you Russia
all three go away
if the bots can't hear you the matter if
people know that the bots are there then
maybe they'll you know they'll well
delve what they'll get ashamed but lots
had to feel ashamed 41 Action News
morning show before you I love more than
who shows up ELISA text me is that a
graph
it's always better than oh come on so
long called so much damage inappropriate
like I feel it's kind of been
appropriate when people call as a
business for like a business anything
right lay out like a friend though
calling me for so you get so you get
like a hundred times in for me but okay
do you want to like plants like a hey I
mean you know hey I'm up in the city
tonight what are you up to
don't call me and say that she text me
then like an hour later you're like hour
later I respond quickly on hold request
that was for the best form of
collaboration this is seriously I'm not
distracted
so when Georgia takes over the wheel
it's because there's a six minute time
around gets lower and lower and one day
one day we might have to justify why it
was six minutes and it's honestly just
because of the line six minutes Slim
Shady you're on like that's really wise
at six minutes as most of your life
let's go down this track
did fam become a thing oh man I like it
on fleek stop trying to make that
Lindsay Lohan fell hard you're watching
you're watching let's hang out yeah I've
given up on my dream of Taylor Swift
[Music]
oh yeah the upside our an odyssey
um it's on the camera the camera thing
is flipped around so the giraffe doesn't
really like like it plugs in but it
doesn't fit
why is it upside down oh well that is a
deep existential question when those
connectors are greedy bankers
after African you contribute a cloud
back-end or modeling no so those parts
aren't open source these are the parts
we keep as a company
it also be hard to sort of like
crowdsource any useful stuff for that we
did common coloring we were just like
hollering I mean that's like you have
the simplest way sort of be able to
contribute to that
as we have new stuff little apartment
fun super - gross unsupervised sick
oh how can you report the pods
that's a good question I'm gonna share
if never use periscope from a user
perspective but maybe if you like click
on their profile I don't know what you
can do on periscope
but it'd be great if you can click on
the profile be like this is about
right here okay so so since there's no
traffic lights we're gonna make bridges
so we're gonna pass under this bridge
and I'm gonna tell you who this bridge
is brought to you by ready wait wait let
me record this for our homie record this
for a homie this bridge passing under
this bridge safely and smoothly with a
Luhan has been brought to you by Bitcoin
cash don't get it twisted it's not
Bitcoin Bitcoin has high transaction
fees and you know it's it's it's smaller
the blocks are small it's too expensive
to get in if you miss the Bitcoin bubble
you should get in on Bitcoin it's the
future pick when it's real it's really
like what are you gotta do Bitcoin - I
wish we had a wallet prepared right now
we could have our big cash
people that we used to get anything they
did Vikrant comm we download the end
payment I love download the app they
have a wallet wow I was just chauffeur
all the time
we're honestly not being paid by we'd
like to be paid by Bitcoin cash those
put it put a show it to the skull peas
this is this is our if you want to send
this yeah everybody if you want to send
us if you're enjoying this but you can't
send this big point I'll share only
Bitcoin cash that is BCH it's super easy
to get just by aetherium or light coming
on coin days and then send it over to
finance where you can do a quick note of
crypto job the good cash bros just get
you just throw my address a like no
there's nothing sketchy about public
keys - pro another bridge mother bridge
this bridge brought to you by the boys
magic use the age that has a version of
Bitcoin don't call it B CH get it
twisted bros
I've seen a house
there's no Little House on the Prairie
that's fake news I'm withdrawing from
your wallet and it's gone damn gas money
now that I would still try to buy the
light going on coin Basel intend to get
over to finance what lights how it says
maintenance required let me see I always
see if your private key show
you have a little bit more cash in there
wait is that just that just get sent in
their journey how someone already had it
I've already had pick on cash Erickson
alright good luck trying to scan that QR
code from the Paris yeah that's not
gonna work I will read out the address
under this next bridge is that better
you guys we write it down no no let's
read out the address because you know
the bridges you know they're brought to
you by cash oh I know I kind of like it
this bridge is brought to you by B cash
the address is 1l 6 600 s 8 WQ and X
[Music]
what did you say about litecoin like
when bros I don't have any light coin so
I shouldn't show for light coin which is
by etherium bros I have a lot of
theorems yeah I had more I had more
theorems but then I deleted some and
that was a great tragedy
ya gotta pick ones at a team yeah
oh my gosh Jake is finally watching this
just this is addressing these Batak
really just read his user name it
realizes we've been showing hard every
bridge there's no red lights here some
bridges okay why is there a wire by the
viewer this wire so the Toyota
unfortunately can't get power from the
from the connector up top except from
when the cars running so we had to run
this wire all the way down to the opt
for we're doing a better solution to get
power from here yeah I think you know
you can get power while the car is
running this is only for when the car is
stopped so it will work just out of the
box if you set the switches right on the
giraffe yeah if you flip switch three on
your giraffe that'll tie the ignition
power to panda power and charge your yun
whenever the car is on you guys like
this is really this is the kind of
that should be level 3 like this Hilary
this is upset man I know but seriously
for truck stop just imagine you could
just send your truck go to Kansas City
yo let's give a shout-out to that man be
meted 3.8 million miles we met a truck
driver Salt Lake City meet up your
grandma's car is nice thank you
a macaque I saw just one night I was 18
it's got my Porsche Boxster right manual
stick shift car right I pull up and pull
up at a red light two girls in the car
next to me and I stall in there like
daddy's car doing a call we're home
we're not opposed to it so you want
right now just yeah like like you got my
email send me emails chat a periscope
right now we know you're busy mr. musk
this is the future Yanis what up ,
because if you go below 7
is this is this the future yes you are
you are you're living in the future with
us right now
wait this guy dude this guy's are
slowing down I that's good too forever
I'm gonna drive across the country yeah
you wanna wait for you to do this
grouting you promise by the end of the
year
do you want a busy man he's three
companies no no no you no one has two
companies now Tesla bought Solar City
boring company all the boring company
and neuro-link and opening I want to
start alright alright let's let's let's
let him in and see what the scope is
think so you guys know that there's a
communist bakery in the mission
it's called Aris Camden Cisco you know
workers of the world unite I'm a fan
right um but I want to open a fascist
bagel store shops as babies but there's
no good place for bagels in San
Francisco's really bad all right I think
the fascist angle will bring in lots of
press I think he'd be a super popular
spot to hang out for a good bagel
you could have protesters even they
could come in enjoy a hot sis bagel yeah
only butter them and only like one mm
you want more more like less some words
no no no no get out get out
set the Soup Nazi but for Baker's all
right it's kind of lightly toasted with
butter honey this is the best part of
the butter so that's that's business
idea one business idea too is okay you
guys go to private islands online.com
you can buy a private island right the
real question is how do you monetize
your private island and here's my idea
it's called the lost experience yeah for
like ten thousand dollars for two weeks
your opponent on the island with 79
other people
and you get to experience lost right
like we'll set up like mysteries
and it'll be it'll be crazy and you know
things will go down and everything this
is like my transition to actually build
Beijing bitcoins ask how long they go
depends how long feel like talking to
you guys yeah I mean what what else are
we doing prayer is the prayer lots of
Perry I like those things motors this
bridge is put to you by they could cash
Emily go out right now get some Bitcoin
caches in future Bitcoin they got big
box
like the cars the cars drive you guys I
trust me the gas and brake are a lot
easier to do on a road like this than
this don't think so this car is actually
pretty he's from the Kansas side
oh that's just there like a lot of beef
like between the Sun y'all even after
the war after the war yeah I don't know
it's been it's been a while is there
still deep between the north and the
south
and there's like a Missouri River that
divides
it's not really about the curving right
so there's a lot of factors that go into
one of them is obviously you speed so
what the Aeon limits is the amount of
torque it can put on the steering wheel
on the Toyota we don't we limit more
than 2r we also limit the rate at which
torque can be applied is you don't want
to like instantaneously apply even the
full small amount of torque
kind of like Ford pickups are selling
pretty well what made it not what made
us not want to do it for it oh this is
this is the car question oh man that
bridge by the way it's about to you dad
fridge was brought to you by a theorem
you know we never would children without
Yoda Yoda is a terrible tangles aren't
real proud but you look at how that
shit's supposed to work it doesn't work
they also invented a quantum resistant
hash function that uses trinary this
make no sense at all yeah I always still
like the just show how the rational
bubble is I'm not strong we don't only
join on straight lines but this is all
you have in Kansas if you want to see
something else you can watch our
periscope from yesterday where we drove
through the urban sprawl of Colorado
yeah straight I mean it's not like you
know we get like we could go right but
it would kind of be the wrong answer
[Laughter]
I washed which has some issues and bugs
but it's cool Ben will be complaining
about them in the 11 o'clock meeting and
he keeps shilling for gas money
we're on reddit now yeah cash bro yeah
we get something that's brought to you
by I write it on a card and shake your
balance you got the cash
no we're splitting all the BK so it's in
three ways hey wait how would you get
yeah how much how much cash is that nine
bucks they say you know why cause I got
some great shown to do when we hit this
bridge oh that's amazing go cash than we
did yeah Ben wants to buy some comic
product prize this bridge right here is
brought to you by Bitcoin cash vouchers
Bitcoin cash let me tell you something
it's impossible to send nine dollars
with Bitcoin because you have to pay $19
and transactions activist to Bitcoin
cashless transaction fees that are under
a cent they're incredible because the
blocks are our big Bitcoin cash is the
future of Bitcoin you heard it here
first guys I feel like those guys wanna
make fun of on the podcast it's like
this podcaster talk to you by audible
yes have you ever been in the end of an
audiobook download if you're listening
to me right now you'll also want to
listen
to this podcast this podcast from that
one isn't worried should we write it
down on a piece of did that work well
what's your BCH address have a security
of Bitcoin built a real crypto
technology unlike iota which is built on
open pilot keep us stable -
yeah they got a detective there so you
call you yeah we don't we're gonna do it
this way we don't want you on Bob where
our seatbelt for obvious reasons
what up scope is so please Eddie get it
on this piece of paper so what up scope
please
what's up what are you gonna call how
many we got Frodo's we got 74
people watching this thank you so
much
we're not doing an official stop in
Minneapolis honestly why are we even
talking about self-driving cars you rock
thank you so much we can't say that
goodness like making a road trip thank
you thank you Scopus I just read it read
it read it read it did it Wow
you always do that like read everywhere
they like it's like crypto millionaire
they're like we're gonna turn one guy
into a crypto millionaire has done more
for redistributing the wealth yeah it's
gonna do not know we're late seriously
now
you know now they're like be seasoned by
again ship we are redistributing the
wealth Syrians love it watching from
chanceless what up I'm from Tampa town
up Tampa where's Kitty Pryde from know I
noticed Florida back or did Claire's in
Florida
remember that's medicine with a things
they pierce through here so deep here so
that I can sketch that mysterious right
feel like you know really good place to
get it Pierce yeah yeah yeah you just
said you did you neither ferocious look
for your parents you were 12
turn the nice children nice and slow
beyond this guy yeah all right
someone watching from Belarus
man that's long-distance internet let's
try to cost me more don't worry because
red should start accepting
- in the store I heard some rumors we
love to talk about those I heard bid
pays for the start accepting picked my
cash yeah which would be so much better
than Bitcoin because the transaction
fees are absolutely insane with that go
ahead
yeah well we will accept it to be honest
if base we're just to pick my cash we'll
accept it crypto man there's no such
thing as another traitor this is just a
great reason to buy big more cash we're
not happy like back when bigger cash
like seven rows like sell sell sell I'm
like mad bro they already did they have
any accepted but sell your Bitcoin gold
Gold yeah they switch the hash algorithm
fight against biting but we do what it
takes to think we can we do like things
that use GPUs to mine because if things
use GPUs to mine that is driving the
price of GPUs down drive the volumes up
and making our models train faster so we
are big fan of uh GPU fine
you better give use then he wants to
send us you can do Oh yo we just bought
one of those b1 hundreds it was a Titan
fee so happy that Nvidia finally found a
new letter not ex tax are those cash
absolutely always pay the government you
guys the government is your friend
absolutely man I don't see what they
like they'll just wrote a lot of tax
right like nothing's free man there's no
such thing as pretty lunch
that was that was see you guys eat there
like please sticker cash
Bridge coming up here is brought to you
by
let her be
it's my letters
what's that call very soon it's gonna be
like this is NPR you can send the flip
connected the flip we don't know gross
you can flip it you could oh you know
what you should do you should write a
letter to Hahn to be like hi I'm 12
years old and what is this
no but the schematics for the giraffe
are you can see you know what what pens
you need flip you can make you know
they flip silly and they're right in the
Neo repo they're an evil god make me
very accessible
make up upside down
right now
possible to send Bitcoin without high
transaction fees
yeah
so eight
guys you need relaxed music by driving
so safety so what do we got I've got
suggestions do some a travel apply this
for you this week what are you you don't
have fly that's it
yeah
dosoo no internet
which app to use to manage my cash easy
becoming calm in the back so all we
really have downloaded is like some rap
and babies
[Music]
dark right now roll
can the antique voice anybody
quit dot-com that is all you don't get
it yeah it's a big window not wallet
Betty let's get let's get that on my
last shipment smoke to receive the
address or the address
and was gonna come try and steal my
Pikmin hey baby boy ready ready
wait how does that phone have a
perception 88 really is better than they
really care about middle-american AT&T
if you're out there unless they if you
could
he's scoping so nah scopes are not free
we have a great sponsor
use Tebow
oh we had some internet no quickly
before it goes away
telescope is doing project filed away
have fun outside peace thanks Dan
we should be talking like this should
actually show you should just show bars
we should show whether you have
we're searching
we haven't started does that work
will complain about that my meeting you
did it once
I got I got actually
guys I'm chillin Frick Burt be cash
fundraiser on my grandson now the New
York my public is
we should just seek to put our music
offline
why don't we stop that you know that you
want me
why is there no audio fit feedback from
me Oh what do you mean like to speak
he knows you you he knows me you said my
name wrong
okay p06 ninja you no no no someone else
because you know his name
[Music]
and of course shout out to pick one
we never I mean the donation tribe never
ends have you seen Jimmy Wales Judy wins
do you guys know that you were gonna
give you money it's going to fund Jimmy
Wales its first class
on the road again yeah donate to a
convenient guys instead of reading the
news you should just read with the radio
to pedia
urge to speak on this year you know all
conferences start out cool and end up
becoming either professional or run by
[Music]
someone just reported the bot I don't
know if your body said that but I really
hope you could wipe out the bots are
reporting themselves yeah you know whose
report me Wow so our theory about the
box is that they made by Facebook to try
to make the narrow scope experience
worse
[Music]
it's like nothing for miles you guys by
the way that's a great book no laptop
get go exit you guys should all read
that it's a great book it's good like
cuts through some human nature
I reported a box not a bottle
like how do you know if someone's not a
bot now I like question everything you
know I really don't believe you're about
to catch all the difference anymore like
we really should start thinking about
that
so you very good point to be cash no you
know - because you don't need to you can
fly Bitcoin cash but you know you can
convert unless I'm I thought that
doesn't know it's a fob but let's be
real aren't we all thoughts that we
don't know where by Beijing bitcoins are
self-aware bot that's true yeah now you
know facing big legends so don't give it
up real good
some ever received it maybe it's big
where they don't spend it
j-jake now this truck
the network Oh what is it open pilot a
ba guys isn't that much of a difference
my dream in 10 years is to be dating an
AI yeah dad I got it kidding I'm really
excited for the future y'all but like I
mean like really
she's just gonna be in the advertising
circle yeah you're just gonna get you're
scared of getting advertised your life
away George it's happening with your
girlfriend don't build your girlfriend
that's freaky it's me George screeching
from unison Kansas City I think people
are receiving someone called out you
honest a Toshi
guys it's Craig right like a next month
suck
take movie years with deaf movie knows
the bathroom that movie had so much
potential not like their bread scene and
like oh this is gonna be so good and
that kind of transcendent so endless
I've got the script of transcendence and
loved it I'm gonna saw the movie in a
terrible Johnny Depp sucks
Johnny Depp fell hard
after Pulp Fiction and the
No then someone can get ya no no we'll
do like what they do
let's give some to people don't need
like last year who was the Moses opposed
the Patriots versus the Cardinals he
wasn't John Travolta damn I Johnny Depp
the only thing he's ever good in then
was the first pirate yeah Charlie and
the Chocolate Factory
if you set us 30 bucks to be cash right
now
Bitcoin cash right now yeah
like Kansas City no this is not good
they're even holding cattle in their
cattle or sheep I just saw them what's
brought you my cargo cargo the biggest
farming that nobody knows if you want
your family farm to be purchased up you
want to consider and we'll be next in
Omaha we were doing Sioux Falls and
Minneapolis the same thing well no so
we're not hosting anything in
Minneapolis are all we're driving to the
office that night the dates on the
t-shirt is slightly wrong no dates are
completely right locations work we're
holding meetups are so we should have
been stars oh yeah you can add that with
wite-out
modify your t-shirt oh my it
open-sourced where Sullivan's in the
t-shirt they're not open sores t-shirts
are our intellectual property pretty
connect and they're oh my god it smells
like cattle
they are watching I said all right y'all
you eat burgers it's good to know where
they come from one day we'll all have
lab-grown meat will taste better than
any meat you've ever imagined we can end
all this terrible suffering
the transport they don't just kill them
where they were I'm not ready to die
yeah yeah maybe they're gonna be in a
what do you do with cattle decide to
kill them or velcro
we've been around again
post-rock how fast can your car breaks
like house I guess how strongly can your
car break for mileage and dewpoint 3 G's